Al-Zubair Mohammed Khudair

Bayji/Salah Al-Deen Tel: 07722399335 zz589993@gmail.com

Nationality: Iraq Gender: Male

Very enthusiastic, motivated and dependable professional individual, I have gained tremendous experience and well developed my skills on how to communicate and approach people from much diversified culture and backgrounds. I am an easy approachable and flexible person always can fit in any team, work and organize myself and my time under workload pressure.

WORK HISTORY

Apr 2018 – May 2019 Mercy Hands Guard

Tikrit, Iraq

- Build capacity on the program's approaches and expected results through active participation in staff training and orientation as well as full engagement in the program's processes.
- Ensure the implementation of agreed plans at the field level to achieve quality results on time.
- Mobilize communities (leaders, parents, etc.) and disseminate information about the project to promote community support.
- Hold regular meetings with stakeholders including schools, local councils and other
 organizations serving children and community to familiarize them with the projects and its
 objectives and engage them in the process
- Submit regular updates, reports and case studies on success stories and lessons learned
- Collect data from the field in line with program indicators.
- Liaise with other stakeholders, including schools, local leaders, partners and participates in relevant meetings.
- Represent programming with local government, NGOs, communities and within SEDO as appropriate.

Mar 2017 – Feb 2018 Tikrit Municipality Council

Tikrit, Iraq

Watchman

- Secure premises and personnel by patrolling property; monitoring surveillance equipment; inspecting buildings, equipment, and access points; permitting entry.
- Prevent losses and damage by reporting irregularities; informing violators of policy and procedures; restraining trespassers.
- Complete reports by recording observations, information, occurrences, and surveillance activities; interviewing witnesses; obtaining signatures.
- Ensure operation of equipment by completing preventive maintenance requirements; following manufacturer's instructions; troubleshooting malfunctions; calling for repairs; evaluating new equipment and techniques.
- Contribute to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.

Apr 2016 – Jan 2017 The Independent High Electoral Commission of Iraq, Tikrit

Tikrit, Iraq

Data Entry Operator

- Insert customer and account data by inputting text based and numerical information from source documents within time limits
- Compile, verify accuracy and sort information according to priorities to prepare source data for computer entry
- Review data for deficiencies or errors, correct any incompatibilities if possible and check output
- Research and obtain further information for incomplete documents
- Generate reports, store completed work in designated locations and perform backup operations

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TIKRIT

Bachelor in Economics

Tikrit, Iraq

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Advanced user of Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, and PowerPoint; as well as outlook
- Good command in training and capacity building of community
- Able to prioritize, communicate effectively, and meet deadlines.
- Ability to work under pressure
- Experience working with people from different backgrounds
- Good interpersonal skills in team leadership, research, analysis, and decision-making

LANGUAGES

- Arabic language(Native), Reading, writing and speaking Fluency
- English language, Reading, writing and speaking I understand